multiplan.com 2007-05-06

# MultiPlan, Inc., Welcomes you to MultiPlan.com

**MultiPlan.com Privacy Policy**  
Welcome to the MultiPlan, Inc. website. This section explains our policy regarding any personal information you might supply to us when you visit this website. Our goal is to protect your information and provide you with the best possible web experience. 

In general, you can visit MultiPlan.com without telling us who you are or reveling any personal information about yourself. We track Internet addresses of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. 

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies". A cookie is a small piece of information that a Web site stores in the Web browser on your computer and can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that set the cookie. We use cookies for a number of reasons, for example, to store your user name and password so you do not have to input it every time you visit our site. Also, we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. You can always set up your web browser to inform you when cookies are being set or prevent cookies from being set. 

**Security**  
Cookies cannot be used to obtain data from your hard drive, get your e-mail address or steal sensitive or personal information about you. The only way that any private information could be part of the cookie file would be if you personally gave that information to the web server. Also, each cookie can only be read by the server that set it, so strange servers cannot view or steal the information in a cookie that you have previously accepted. The MultiPlan, Inc. web site does not store any personal information in a visitor's cookie. 

Note that computer viruses are not passed through setting or the use of cookies. Also, you as the visitor can disable the use of cookies in your web browser. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. To remove your information from our database and to stop receiving communication from us and our partners send an email to [webmail@multiplan.com](mailto:webmail@multiplan.com) or return to the registration log-in screen and change your user preferences. 

**Third Party Disclaimer**  
This privacy policy does not apply to any other web site you go to from this site, including those to which we have provided links for your convenience. If you are concerned about or interested in the privacy practices of the other web sites you visit, you may wish to review their posted privacy statements or contact them directly. 

**Correct/Update**  
You may modify your personal information at any time by sending e-mail to [webmail@multiplan.com](mailto:webmail@multiplan.com) or by visiting the user registration login page and changing the items you wish to updated or deleted. 

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have further questions or concerned please visit the "Contact Us" section of the website or simply sending an e-mail to [webmail@multiplan.com](mailto:webmail@multiplan.com) for all general inquires.
